memolink.com 2016-03-14

# Cash Back Sites, Coupons, Rewards & Surveys | Memolink

Have you ever wondered what we do with the information you give us, but maybe you didn’t want to take the time to read through a long, legal document to find out? Well, we’ve made a change that will make understanding how we collect, use, and protect your information easier and less time consuming. We’re proud of how we adhere to best practices when it comes to your information and we want you to feel good about it too. Below are the highlights of the full Memolink.com Privacy Statement. Click into any section to read additional details. 

**Personal Information**

 _More Details_

  * • When you register for Memolink.com we will ask you to provide various personal and other information.
  * • If you join using a social login and provide consent, we may collect certain social information including your interests, email address, birthday, city, and likes.
  * • The information we collect may be combined with information obtained from Memolink Surveys and other business partners.
  * • We use cookies and other technologies to keep track of your point-earning actions so we can credit Memolink Points to your account and to offer a  
customized experience.

**Uses of Information**

 _More Details_

  * • We use the information we collect to provide the Memolink.com rewards program service. Our services may include providing you with personalized content based  
     on the information we have about you and your interests.
  * • We use your information to inform you of other products or services offered by Memolink.com and its business partners, and to send you relevant survey invitations.
  * • We do not sell, rent, or lease your information; however, in order to help provide our services, we may occasionally provide your non-personally identifiable  
     information to other companies that work on our behalf and are bound by confidentiality obligations to protect your information.
  * • With respect to any information that we collect from your social login: 
    * • We will not sell your data or your friend’s data
    * • We will not post on your behalf without your permission
    * • We will not send messages to your friends without your permission
    * • We will not spam you with unsolicited emails

  * To stop receiving promotion email, please follow the instructions in any email. See the email communication section of the full privacy statement for additional details.
  * To view and edit your personal information, go to the access section of the full privacy statement.

**How to Contact Us**

For more information about our privacy practices contact us [here](mailto:support@memolink.com). 

**Consumer Protection Information**

**Memolink.com Privacy Statement**

It is important that you fully understand what happens to the information we gather from you through the use of our Website located at, or linked to, [www.memolink.com](http://www.memolink.com/). Please read this Privacy Statement carefully to understand how we will use and protect your personal information. 

We will use your personal information only as described in this Statement. Each time you use Memolink.com, the current version of the Privacy Statement will apply. Accordingly, when you use Memolink.com, you should check the date of this Statement and review any changes since the last version. 

**Collection of Your Personal Information**

Upon registration, we will ask a user to provide personal information such as name, email address, physical mailing address, and phone number(s). We may also collect other information about you, known as demographic and profile data, such as your zip code, annual income, preferences, or age. After registration, we may ask for additional personal information from you, such as shipping address and proof of address. By completing Memolink surveys, you will be providing us with additional personal information or data.

  * • If a user joins using a social login, such as Facebook or Twitter and provides consent, we may collect social information including your interests, email address,   
birthday, city, and likes. Memolink utilizes this information to personalize your experience to show you the most relevant content, such as displaying or emailing  
deals from your favorite stores, surveys targeted to your age or city, and displaying or emailing offers that may be of more interest to you. 

We may ask our business partners to provide additional information about you, such as purchases you made, products ordered, order number, the date and time of the purchase, and the email address used for the purchase. 

When you receive email from Memolink.com, we may use Web beacons and customized links (or similar technologies) to determine whether the email has been opened and whether you clicked on a link in the email, so we can award you memolink points. 

Information collected through registration may be combined with demographic information that you provide through completion of Memolink surveys. We may collect information about your interaction with our Site and services. For example, we may use website analytics tools on our Site to retrieve information from your browser, including the site you came from, the search engine(s) and the keywords you used to find our Site, the pages you view within our Site, your browser add-ons, and your browser's width and height. We may also use technologies, such as cookies and Web beacons, to collect information about the pages you view, the links you click and other actions you take on our Sites and services. Additionally, we collect certain standard information that your browser sends to every website you visit, such as your IP address, browser type and language, access times and referring Web site addresses.   

**Use of Your Personal Information**

Memolink.com collects and uses your personal information and other data to operate and improve our Site and services. These uses may include providing you with more effective member support service; making our Site easier to use; performing research and analysis aimed at improving our Site and services; and providing you with content and communication that are relevant to your interests and preferences, such as an alert that a coupon is available for one of your favorite stores. 

We also use your personal information to communicate with you. We may contact you via email with important account information critical to your membership with us, with offerings or surveys from our business partners, or with responses to your member support inquiries. We may use the physical address and proof of address that you provide to ship rewards and to prevent fraud. For more information about the use of information for communication, see the Communication Preferences section below. 

The following protections apply to any information that we obtain from your social login: 

  * • We will not sell the social profile data of users or their friends to third parties. This includes not sharing any social profile data with a third party unless the third party  
  acts on our behalf (for example, as a vendor or service provider).
  * • We will not publicly post to a user’s social network account on behalf of a user without the user’s explicit permission.
  * • We will not use personal information obtained via social login to send newsletters or promotional emails unless users have opted-in to such notifications. You can   
  opt out of newsletters at any time.
  * • We will not send private messages to a user’s friend(s) unless prompted by the user.
  * • We will not spam you with unsolicited emails.
  * • We will delete all of your information obtained from a social login (including friend data) if you ask us to delete such information, unless we are required to keep it  
   by law, regulation or separate agreement (however, we may keep aggregate data if no information indentifying a specific person could be inferred or created from it). 

**Use of Cookies**

A “cookie” is a small piece of data we store on your hard drive. When you logon to our Site using your email address and password or social login, we store a unique session ID number in a cookie on your hard drive. A cookie is used to help us keep track of the points you earn during a visit to our Site. For convenience, a cookie is also used to allow you to move from page to page without having to login again on each page. You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but, if you prefer, you can usually change your browser setting to decline cookies. If you choose to decline cookies on our Site, you may still use our Site, however you will be prompted to logon multiple times and you risk not receiving credit for the points you have earned.   

**Use of Web Beacons**

Memolink.com Web pages or email communication may contain tiny electronic images known as Web beacons, also known as clear gifs, single-pixel gifs, pixel tags, or action tags. Similar in function to cookies, a Web beacon may be used to track your movement from page to page on our Site and to let us know if you have opened an email that we sent you. 

We use Web beacons to help us manage content on our Site by informing us of what content is most viewed by our users, and to help us measure advertising effectiveness. 

We may also employ Web beacons from third parties in order to help us compile aggregated statistics regarding the effectiveness of our content, advertising, or other operations of our Site. We prohibit Web beacons on our Site from being used by third parties to collect or access your personal information.   

**Sharing of Your Personal Information**

Except as described in this statement, we will not disclose your personal information outside of Memolink.com without your consent. Memolink may disclose personal information if required to do so by law or if it believes that such action is necessary to protect and defend the rights, property or personal safety of Memolink and its website, visitors to the website and members of our services. Your personal information may be transferred in connection with a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition, insolvency, or asset sale. In order to provide our products and services, we may hire other companies to provide limited services on our behalf, such as to send email, to perform statistical analysis of our services, to provide member support, or to carry out reward fulfillment. These service providers will be permitted to obtain only the personal information they need to perform their functions. They are required to maintain the confidentiality of the information and are prohibited from using it for any other purpose. 

Our website contains links to the sites of third parties. When you visit these sites, please consult those sites' individual privacy statements in order to determine how they treat user information. Memolink is not responsible for the privacy statements or the content of such sites, and the privacy practices of other Websites and companies are not covered by this statement. Memolink requests that users report any and all concerns about our business partners' privacy practices directly to us as outlined in the Contacting Us section below.   

**Accessing Your Personal Information**

Memolink users are able to change their personal information at any time, The fastest way to change personal information is to logon to Memolink.com and go to the Edit Profile section of the My Account area, then click “Edit Personal Info.” If for some reason this page does not work, or you have any questions, you may contact us as outlined in the Contacting Us section below.   

**Communication Preferences**

You may choose whether you would like to receive marketing communications and offers promoted by Memolink.com or our third party business partners. If you do not wish to receive marketing communications from us, you may opt out at any time. These choices do not apply to the receipt of specific administrative notices that are required by law, regulation, or as needed to service your account. 

**Email Communication**

Because email is integral part of the program, you sign up to receive email targeted to your interests at the time of registration. If you do not wish to receive email messages, known as Memolink Emails, you may opt out by updating your Email Preferences at any time on the Memolink.com Site, or by clicking on the “Unsubscribe” link at the bottom of any Memolink Emails. Your other unsubscribe options also include sending an unsubscribe request in the mail to the physical address contained in every Memolink Emails or by sending an unsubscribe request to our Member Support department. Whatever method you choose, you will be removed from our mailing list within no more than 7 business days, but usually within 24 hours.   

**Security**

Memolink is committed to protecting the security of your personal information. We use a variety of security technologies and procedures to protect your personal information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. For example, we store your personal information on computer systems with limited access, which are stored in a secure environment. All of your information is restricted in our offices too. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, our Member Support department) are granted access to your personal information. Our employees must use password-protected screen-savers when they leave their desks. When they return, they must re-enter their password to regain access. 

A password is used to help protect your account and personal information. It is your responsibility to keep your password confidential. Do not share this information with anyone. If you are sharing a computer with anyone you should always logout before leaving our Site or service to protect access to your information from subsequent users. If you feel your password has been compromised, you should change it immediately. After you have finished using our Site, you should log out of your Memolink.com account and close your browser so that no unauthorized persons can use our Site under your name and account information.   

**Changes to This Privacy Statement**

We will occasionally update this Privacy Statement to reflect changes in our services and customer feedback. When we post changes to this Statement, we will revise the "last updated" date at the top of this statement. If there are material changes to this statement regarding how Memolink.com will use or share your personal information, we will notify you either by prominently posting a notice of such changes prior to implementing the change or by directly sending you a notification. We encourage you to periodically review this statement to be informed of how Memolink.com is protecting your information.   

**Contacting Us**

If you have any questions or concerns about your privacy at Memolink.com, please contact us at [support@memolink.com](mailto:support@memolink.com) or you may contact us in writing at: 

Memolink.com Member Support – Security & Privacy  
2000 S. Colorado Blvd.  
Tower 1, Suite 7000  
Denver, CO 80222
